postgully.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy | Daily Dose of Posts

We as Postgully.com regard Your protection and it is essential to us.

We regard your protection in regards to any data you share on postgully.com. We have plot our protection arrangement to tell our client how we gather, utilize, impart, reveal and utilize your own data. The subtle elements of our security strategies are said beneath.

Your own data will be gathered by every single reasonable mean with your insight and assent. We will approach you to information exchange for our pamphlet, or subscribe to our news notices. It will be you who will permit us and give your own subtle elements like Email address, telephone, contact points of interest and so on.

We will tell you the motivation behind the data we are asking earlier or after the gathering your own points of interest.

We will utilize your own data exclusively to fulfill purposes determined by us amid information exchange.

Individual information ought to be important to the reasons for which it is to be utilized, and, to the degree essential for those reasons, ought to be precise, entire, and a la mode.

We will ensure individual data by utilizing sensible security shields against misfortune or burglary, and additionally unapproved get to, revelation, replicating, utilize or change.

We will make promptly accessible to clients data about our arrangements and works on identifying with the administration of individual data.

We will just hold individual data for whatever length of time that important for the satisfaction of those reasons.

We are focused on directing our business as per these standards keeping in mind the end goal to guarantee that the secrecy of individual data is secured and kept up. Postgully.com may change this security strategy every now and then at Postgully’s sole tact.

 **Information We Collect & How We Use It**

postgully.com We don’t collect data in order to advertise to you. The tracking we do at postgully.com is to make our product work as well as possible.

In order to give you the best possible experience using postgully.com, we collect information from your interactions with our network. Some of this information, you actively tell us (such as your email address, which we use to track your account or communicate with you). Other information, we collect based on actions you take while using postgully.com, such as what pages you access and your interactions with our product features (like highlights, follows, and applause). This information includes records of those interactions, your Internet Protocol address, information about your device (such as device or browser type), and referral information.

We use this information to:

  * provide, test, improve, promote and personalize our Services
  * fight spam and other forms of abuse
  * generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how people use our Services

When you create your postgully.com account, and authenticate with a third-party service (like Twitter, Facebook or Google) we may collect, store, and periodically update information associated with that third-party account, such as your lists of friends or followers. We will never publish through your third-party account without your permission.

 **Google Login**  
1.  
In order to provide a customized user experience with regards News, alerts, announcement, government policies, job alerts etc, we would be requiring support of the Gmail API. We intend to provide e-mail support to users to aggregate their online activities, which would involve use of features like mail merge, user activity, etc.  
Keeping such mails away from the Spam folder would be of utmost importance. We would be explaining our users the need for their Gmail account access to ensure that our mails are never deleted by mistake or are never left unread if they land in their spam folder.

2\. We have multiple websites ranging from Business News, Motivational website, Latest coupon deals, Astrology etc. which makes social profiling of our user base extremely important. Separate authentication shall be done for each website post which information can be personalized to create a custom user experience.

Through these multiple websites there would be significant interchange of data between Gmail, Google Calendar, Google Drive, Google Analytics and Youtube for which we intend to develop a CRM tool.

Since all websites will have an interconnected user base, keeping them logged in though a single Gmail login would immensely help us. We would be explaining our users the need for their Gmail account access to ensure that our mails are never deleted by mistake or are never left unread if they land in their spam folder.

3\. By allowing google login, we will moving our emails from spam to inbox. We have received complains from our subscribers that they don’t receive our emails or they receive emails or they get it spam even if they move it to inbox folder and mark it as important. So by enabling google login, the user must be giving us permission to move our emails from spam to inbox so that you never miss our updates.

 **Existence of Automated Decision-making**

We collects and stores personal data about its users to customize reading. This includes automated decision-making to promote content tailored to the preferences and interests indicated by the user, and to their browsing history and network interactions.

We also filters content for the purposes of fighting and preventing spam, fraud, and other forms of abuse.

 **Categories of Personal Data Collected**

  * Username
  * Display name
  * Bio
  * Avatar image
  * Email address (non-public)
  * Google Api consent
  * Session activity (security)
  * Linked social media accounts (optional)
  * IP address
  * Browser information
  * Reading history (on com network only)
  * Network interactions (recommends, follows, etc.)
  * Posts, responses, or series published by user

 **Email from  postgully.com**

we’ll send you emails about your account, service changes or new policies. You can’t opt out of this type of “transactional” email (unless you delete your account). But you can opt out of non-administrative emails such as digests, newsletters, and activity notifications through your account.

When you interact with an email sent from postgully.com (such as opening an email or clicking on a particular link in an email), we may receive information about that interaction. We won’t email you to ask for your password or other account information. If you receive such an email, please send it to us so we can investigate.

 **Data Security**

We use encryption (HTTPS/TLS) to protect data transmitted to and from our site. However, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, so we can’t guarantee security. You use the Service at your own risk, and you’re responsible for taking reasonable measures to secure your account.

 **Modifying or Deleting Your Personal Information**

If you have a postgully.com account, you can access, modify or export your personal information, or delete your account.

To protect information from accidental or malicious destruction, we may maintain residual copies for a brief time period. But, if you delete your account, your information and content will be unrecoverable after that time.

 **Data Storage**

postgully.com uses third-party vendors and hosting partners, such as Amazon, for hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology we need to run postgully.com. We maintain two types of logs: server logs and event logs.

 **Tracking & Cookies**

We use browser cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you return to our Services. We use them in various ways, for example to log you in, remember your preferences (such as default language), evaluate email effectiveness, allow our paywall and meter to function, and personalize content and other information.

postgully.com doesn’t track you across the Internet. We track only your interactions within the our network.

Some third-party services that we use to provide the postgully.com Service, such as [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/), may place their own cookies in your browser. This Privacy Policy covers use of cookies by postgully.com only and not the use of cookies by third parties.
